# John Cloed Guarra

Vinzons, Camarines Norte 4603

guarrajohncloed@gmail.com

+639154090993

linkedin.com/in/john-cloed-guarra-92358417a

https://johncloed.github.io/portfolio/

# **Summary**

Certified Google Ads and Facebook Ads specialist who has 3+ years of experience and managed different campaigns for different types of businesses. Help in achieving clients' digital and social media marketing goals, allowing to have a better understanding of how their business performs and generate outstanding results and progress.

#### Expertise includes:

- · Website design and development
- · Digital marketing
- Social Media Manager

## **Experience**

### Web Developer and Digital Marketing Specialist

**ATX Reels** 

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023 (4 months)

Responsibilities:

- Templated web development services
- Designing, setting up, and optimizing Facebook, Instagram, and Google Ads

## **Marketing Advertising Specialist**

Sinclair Media Tech

Jan 2023 - Dec 2023 (1 year)

Responsibilities:

- Monitor website performance, troubleshoot issues, and implement necessary improvements.
- Developing and implementing social media marketing strategies to meet specific business goals, such as increasing brand awareness, driving website traffic, or generating leads.

## **Wordpress Developer and SEO Specialist**

**RADSEO** 

Jul 2022 - Jan 2023 (7 months)

Responsibilities:

- Building and maintaining WordPress websites, themes, and plugins.
- Managing and updating website content, including text, images, and multimedia.
- Implementing basic SEO practices, such as optimizing meta tags, headers, and images for search engines.

#### Education



**Camarines Norte State College** 

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology Aug 2020 - Present

## Microsystem College Foundation Inc.

Senior High School, Computer Programming Jun 2018 - Apr 2020

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Creating Portfolios Using Adobe Express Creative Nation Academy Corporation
- 11th Bicol Youth Congress in Information Technology Camarines Sur Polytechnic Colleges
- **Google Ads Measurement Certification** Google 113627116
- Google Ads Search Certification Google 113583992
- Google Analytics Individual Qualification Google 113682625

#### Skills

Web Development • Bootstrap (Framework) • Java • HTML5 • Advertising • Social Media Marketing • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • C# • MySQL • JavaScript • Unity 3D • PHP • VB.Net • Microsoft Office • Digital Marketing